Through days of thunders
Continuing stolid smiles to wear
We're going on
We nearly carried it to the end
And every whisper
And every beat of windy heart
We're holding on
For the moment when we unite
No face
Is seen at dusk of a raining day
No name
Is spoken in a loud voice
Still still
One day it all
will gone forever  will gone forever
Don’t close your eyes
you’ll gone forever  you’ll gone forever
Just reach the border
To throw your past and go ahead
Hey  light your heart
as we’re led by a winding thread
No face
Is seen at dusk of a raining day
No name
Is spoken with the loud voice
Still still
One day it all
will gone forever  will gone forever
Don’t close your eyes
you’ll gone forever  you’ll gone forever
And we are one  so I promise
One day it all
will gone forever  will gone forever
Don’t close your eyes
you’ll gone forever  you’ll gone forever
There’s no more pain
Which lasts forever
And never severs
Once in the end
The flame was rendered
But living embers
Will burn