Someday you'll come back here
and you'll open up your arms
you'll laugh and say I knew it wouldn't take you long
to realize I was gone
it's only been 3 years
but for me it's been so long
I remember it like yesterday
oh you could say
I've been holding on
I've waited all of my life
for you to make it right
but the time has come and gone
it's faded and lost all it's light
a star that shined so bright
falls from the sky
Don't make a wish that won't come true
I learned that from you
such a long time ago
when you left you said you had to find
a better way of life
this one just wouldn't do
I've waited all of my life
for you to take your time
to find your place
but I learned that this world still turns without you
and you were just a phase and I learned without you
here  I was happier alone
then I ever would've known..
I've waited I've waited
I've waited I've waited I've waited
I've waited all of my my life
for you to take your time
but the time has come and gone
it's faded and lost all it's light
a star that shined so bright
falls from the sky
on this cold December night