Yeah oh
Please don't stand over here
Act like you care so self-aware
I know you were not scared
I could've died  but that isn't fair huh?
But what am I supposed to think?
You weren't there for me
Cause I'm not who I should be for you
You've got a record and a past
Guess that's what makes me the ass
I should've known  I should've cared
How could I have been so unprepared?
Now where does the good boy go to hide away hide the pain?
Cause you won't see me cry when I'm done
What is it that you want from me want from me?
I want you to feel  I want you to feel
I'm a feather in the wind
Carried away by all that you say
Sitting on thin air
I'm a loss to my friends
Too unpersuaded by all they're saying
And you can't pretend to care  yeah
Yeah. I was reckless in the past
I was see-through just like glass
Did all I could to make this last
So how could you be such an ass?
I know where the good boys go to hide the pain hide the pain
But that don't mean I die when you don't
What is it that you want from me want from me?
I want you to feel I want you to feel
I want you to feel  I want you to feel
...good boys go to hide the pain hide the pain
Cause you won't see me cry when I'm done
I know where the good boys go to hide the pain  hide the pain
But that don't mean I die when you don't…