I see your face everywhere that I go
On the clouds in the sky
On the faces of strangers
The birds sing your name
And the fish try to talk
Cause without you the world would be too dark to matter.
You're like the sun
You're so far away
But your light shines on
And brightens each day
When you're not around
You make it worthwhile to expect you.
You're like the sun
You turn on a switch and the gloom is gone
You gave me my life and you carry on
Without ever wanting a thank you
You're like the sun.
Everyone loves you and wants you around
But it's me most of all
For my own selfish reasons
You paint my sky blue
And you spin my earth 'round
So don't leave me alone
'Cause I can't stand to miss you.
You're like the sun
You're so far away
But your light shines on
And brightens each day
When you're not around
You make it worthwhile to expect you.
You're like the sun
You turn on a switch and the gloom is gone
You gave me my life and you carry on
Without ever wanting a thank you
You're like the sun.
You're like the sun
You're so far away
But your light shines on
You brighten my days
When you're not around
You make it worthwhile to expect you.
You're like the sun
You turn on a switch and the gloom is gone
You gave me my life and you carry on
Without ever wanting a thank you
You're like the sun.