Lay awake at night
Wondering how could I
Let it get this way
Through all the pain
I took all the blame
While you cursed my last name
I thought we could get better
Stayed committed like a soldier
Believed we're okay
Now I know that you don't care at all
Time wasted
Gave all of my soul and my heart to someone that would never
Give me the same
I was a fool to believe that you would finally be the one to
Heartbroken now
How you let me down
But somehow deep down I still do
Love you
Now your out all night
Telling your lies
About the way I hurt you
They couldn't see the way
You made me feel ashamed
For choosing to love you
I began to see clearer
That you were just a liar
Stuck in your ways
So now I choose to walk away forever
Time wasted
Gave all of my soul and my heart to someone that would never
Give me the same
I was a fool to believe that you would finally be the one to
Heartbroken now
How you let me down
But somehow deep down I still do
Love you
How could you just throw it all away babe
How could you throw it all away
I stayed with you through all the lies and pain
Through all the lies and pain oh
Tears roll down my eyes
As I now realize
Your love was never truly mine
At all
Time wasted
Gave all of my soul and my heart to someone that would never
Give me the same
I was a fool to believe that you (you) would finally (be the one too)
Heartbroken now
How you let me down
Oh
But somehow (how)  deep down I still do
Love you