People gonna hate let them do it
shine like it ain’t nothing to it
Damn you a major influence
skate like there ain’t nothing doing
Live life don’t say nothing to them
People gonna hate let them do it
shine like it ain’t nothing to it
Damn you a major influence
skate like there ain’t nothing doing
Live life don’t say nothing to them
People telling lies on me
Feeling like Pac
All eyes on me
Whats my next rhyme
Gonna be
Dull mother fuckers can’t never ever
Shine off me?
Wait for it
Don’t worry the My haters is gonna pay for it
chase dreams dumb Niggas chase whores
over sea’s On a great tour
Or maybe I’m just dreaming
It beats being with demons or
A nigga scheming or At least im thinking of an achievement
People talk shit for 4 seasons
For no reason
people dog lebron until lebron show up
when he step on the paint then their guards go up
scores up all the applauds go up
and everybody in the whole damn court goes nuts
People gonna hate let them do it
shine like it ain’t nothing to it
Damn you a major influence
skate like there ain’t nothing doing
Live life don’t say nothing to them
People gonna hate let them do it
shine like it ain’t nothing to it
Damn you a major influence
skate like there ain’t nothing doing
Live life don’t say nothing to them
spectators
side liners
spending days
coming up with sly comments
that’s psychotic why try a tarnish such a fly product?
Why be mad just cause I got? Hey!
I may never know
Wave to the haters That put me on the pedestal talk smack
But they really Know I’m incredible
Unforgettable young blue eyes
the new guy is on schedule
man behind bars and thats minus the federal
Stone giant what the hell
Could some pebbles do
While you Revel In drama Im building revenue
Tell them you’ll get them tomorrow their ain’t Nothing stressing you
Life goes on Lifes goes on
You was the shit even Before those lights went on
They gonna trash you Even if they like your song
People always gonna judge homie right or wrong?
People gonna hate let them do it
shine like it ain’t nothing to it
Damn you a major influence
skate like there ain’t nothing doing
Live life don’t say nothing to them
People gonna hate let them do it
shine like it ain’t nothing to it
Damn you a major influence
skate like there ain’t nothing doing
Live life don’t say nothing to them
We don’t give a damn what you did
We don’t give a damn who are
homie you aint down with the team
We don’t give a damn what you think
We don’t give a damn what you thought
We don’t give a damn what you did
We don’t give a damn who are
homie you aint down with the team
We don’t give a damn what you think
We don’t give a damn what you thought