I’m asleep at the wheel and there’s a curve in the highway
Yet we tear through the night like a peyote migraine
How much further is it  aching  so exquisite
I hope we can stop in time
Now you don’t want to dance  'cause we’re looking right through you
Oh oh  and the clothes that you wear  we don’t mean to stare
Now the sky is on fire and the desert is freezing
Wonder how I’m alive  hen I’m not even breathing
How much further is it  aching  so exquisite
I hope we can stop in time
Now you don’t want to dance  'cause we’re looking right through you
Oh oh and the clothes that you wear we don’t mean to stare
Oh oh  but the people you know  they say what they want to
Oh oh  'cause the truth of it is  we don’t really care