Late nights staying up messaging you
Can I express what I'm feeling for you without revealing truths?
I've been thinking about you lately (lately)
That's a massive understatement  baby
I can't stop thinking about you all day and all night
But Is It Right?
Finally figured it out  I got my head around it.
Although I know I've got to get myself out of this habit.
Of falling for someone who's out of reach it's unrealistic
Mr dream won't become a reality but was it meant to be?
I've been thinking about you lately (lately)
That's a massive understatement  baby
Cause I think about you all day and all night
But Is It Right?
I don't know but I I know how it feels to me
Maybe you're just playing games. A game I don't  wanna play.
Maybe you're just playing games. A game I don't  wanna play
I've been thinking about you lately (lately)
That's a massive understatement  baby
Cause I'm thinking about you all day and all night
But Is It Right
I've been thinking about you lately (lately)
That's a massive understatement  baby
Cause I'm thinking about you all day and all night
But Is It Right