Racking and jacking my mind up.
Cannot be telling the time  I
Don't care  no.
I don't care no.
You send thirty messages drunk
And dirty messages drunk
But I don't look.
No I can't be *** to look.
I could not breathe.
You took your toll on me.
You're suffocating please.
But since I watched you leave
I can see for the first time.
And I can see for the first time.
And I can see for the first time
For the first time.
And I can see for the first time.
You get jealous easily.
You did not make it easy.
But what was I expecting?
It's a very fitting ending.
You say I hurt you bad  well
That was never my intent.
I was looking out for myself
And all of my mental health.
I cannot breathe.
You took your toll on me.
You're suffocating  please.
But since I watched you leave
I can see for the first time.
I can see for the first time
For the first time.
I can see for the first time.
There is no better deduction
There is no better solution
I can see for the first time.
I can see for the first time
For the first time
For the first time.
I can see for the first time.
For the first time
For the first time.