Maybe you hate me
but you dress somebody's suit
because there's no risk
to put on a mask
when we get scared to live
with our back  with our back
Maybe you love me
but you run under the sun and me under the rain
it's so easy
to lose ourselves
when we get scared to love
with every tear with every fear
But you could give me just your money
but I wished just your honey
I burnt your t-shirt  that one with bunny
and now about you nothing more of funny
Maybe we'll meet again
but this not the right life for us
it's so hard
to live our love
when we get scared to see
inside our soul inside our soul
But you could give me just your money
but I wished just your honey
I burnt your t-shirt  that one with bunny
and now about you nothing more of funny
Your mind is closed like an aquarium
mine completly opened like the Colosseum
so nothing about idyll between us
it's not a wrong accent no no no no no no no no
what's wrong is the concept
wrong concept to love
But you could give me just your money
but I wished just your honey
I burnt your t-shirt  that one with bunny
and now about you nothing more of funny
you could give me just your money
but I wished just your honey
I burnt your t-shirt  that one with bunny
and now about you nothing more of funny
Wrong concept  wrong concept to love
wrong concept to love  to love  wrong concept.