Keep on working on your dreams and don't run away
Keep on following your dreams and don't go astray
We searching everywhere for the peace of mind
it's already there but we can not find
I keep struggling for my life but i'm a strong man today
I keep fighting for my rights so much songs to play
So many problems
So many close friends
And when it's gonna rain
how many gonna stand
So many problems
So many close friends
And when it's gonna rain
how many gonna stand
Keep On working on your dreams and don't runaway
Keep on following your dreams and don't go astray
sit back and watch what happens those days
how can I relax for the children of today
We're smart enough to find our own line
We make art and stuff but they just stay blind
So many problems
So many close friends
And when it's gonna rain
how many gonna stand
So many problems So many close friends
And when it's gonna rain
how many gonna stand