I got a lot on my mind
And all of the time
Been trying to do right
I may have the lost the light
But I’m keeping it tight
Never give up the fight no
When my life is a wreck (When my life is a wreck)
Have to keep it all in check (keep it all in check)
Even in the darkest days
Got a trail to blaze
Gonna stick to my ways
I used to be caught in a phase
Where life was a maze
Until I saw the suns rays
When your life is a wreck (life is a wreck)
You got to take that first step
Whoa oh oh oh oh
Paddle on through the waves now
Gonna take me to that place
Whoa oh oh oh oh
Find that fire inside
It’s a fate that you decide
When I feel like I’m losing control
Gotta reach within my soul
And if you’re ever feeling low yeah
Take that first step and go! yeah
Take that first step to the right
Got to find what’s inside
Before we run of time  run out of time  run out of time
Whoa oh oh oh oh
Paddle on through the waves now
Gonna take me to that place
Whoa oh oh oh oh
Find that fire inside
It’s a fate that you decide
that you decide
Whoa oh oh oh oh
I’m paddling on  I’m paddling strong
Find that fire find that fire
Whoa oh oh oh oh
I’m paddling on  I’m paddling strong
Find that fire find that fire
Find that fire find that fire find that fire find that fire