One two three
See you looking at me with those eyes
Four five six
I know that you want this
Am I right? Think I'm right
Let's skip the games
Fast forward to the "What's your name?"
Why take our time? Time
So one two three
Know you heard about me
That's alright
Just hit my line  oh
So come to me
Tonight we don't have to be enemies
Keep it going like it's meant to be
Meant to be  just wait and see
So come with me
And maybe you can touch my body
Don't be scared to take ahold of me
Take me in and breathe  tear me up to pieces
Oh
Get a taste of my bad side
Just a taste of my bad side
You want a taste of my bad side
You wanna know what it feels like
To get a taste of my bad side
La di da di
Bet you'll think it's nothing
Till it drops all at once
Your heart
Oh my oh me
I'm fucking crazy and I can't stop
It'll be fun ha!
Let's skip the games
Fast forward to the "What's your name?"
Why take our time? Time
So oh my oh me
I'm fucking crazy
And I can't stop
So this'll be fun
So come to me
Tonight  we don't have to be enemies
Keep it going like it's meant to be
Meant to be  just wait and see
So come with me
And maybe you can touch my body
Don't be scared to take ahold of me
Take me in and breathe tear me up to pieces
Oh
Get a taste of my bad side
Just a taste of my bad side
You want a taste of my bad side
You wanna know what it feels like
To get a taste of my bad side (Come to me)
Tonight we don't have to be enemies
Just a taste of my bad side
Meant to be meant to be
You want a taste of my bad side (come with me)
And maybe you can touch my body
Just a taste of my bad side (take a hold of me)
You wanna know what it feels like
To get a taste of my bad side
Oh
Get a taste of my bad side
Just a taste of my bad side
You want a taste of my bad side hey!
Taste of my bad side…