He's a whistler when the wind blows
Keeps it simple only whole notes
Plays his hollow tune effortlessly
He just sits there in limbo
Doesn’t listen full of blow holes
Curtains waver the old refrain repeats
A penny for a thought
For pounds of flesh he’s bought
A peso for what not to confess here
The last shall be the first
Wordlessly coerced
Death is not the worst atrocity
There’s a hissing through the window
Like a twisted virtuoso
Warning of a storm brewing again
“To the victor ” goes the intro
Full of whispered innuendo
Time once more for a paranoid crusade
The past shall be reversed
The dead not so accursed
A universe rehearsed in tragedy
He's a whistler he’s a widow
Doesn’t miss her plays it solo
Blissfully ignoring his instinct
Tears bitter on the pillow
Makes his mission not to know more
Curtains flutter the old refrain repeats
Yeah he's a widow
He's a whistler
Oh