Honey I told you something
Sorry I didn’t hear
Maybe there was something
Yeah stuck in your ear
Why is it everytime you say you do you don’t?
Maybe I just thought that you were talking on the phone
Honey you’re looking lovely tonight
Sorry you’re wastin’ time
Baby this ain’t your lucky night
Well tryin’ ain’t a crime
Why is it everytime I’d like to do  you don’t?
Maybe you could try a little romance and a comb
Let’s go back in time
Way back when we were
Lalalala la la lala
Now it’s married life
And a daily strife to be
Lalalalala lalalalala lala
Lalalala la la lala
Honey you’re getting’ older
Yeah and you’re still 29
And maybe things are colder
But honey still you’re mine
Guess it’s easy to forget
We’re more than man and wife
Could it be the “lala-magic” keeping love alive?
Let’s go back in time
Way back when we were
Lalalala la la lala
Back when you and I
Still had time to be
Lalalalala lalalalala lala
Lalalala la la lala
Let’s go back in time
Way back when we were
Lalalala la la lala
Back when you and I
Still had time to be
Lalalalala
Let’s go back in time
Way back when we were
Lalalala la la lala
Now it’s married life
Still we have to try to be
Lalalalala lalalalala lala
Lalalala la la lala