Tears are like diamonds in my eyes
Blind me so now you’re out of sight
It’s enough it’s too late to break this silence
In a rose coloured view of us
either cause could I realize
All your lies would be blades to knifes
To stab me inside
Who will save you from this dark?
Who will fix your selfish heart?
A one way street  that’s how you live
Why do you always take and never give?
Wide awake  yeah I’ve crossed the line
I’m coming home
I’m running back to real life
Through the start
Where I could breathin‘ freely baby
Can’t you see we ran off time
Chasing happiness while you get what you need
There’s nothing left of us but bleeding blades and knifes
Tonight you‘ll know how it feels
A one way street  that’s how you live
Why do you always take and never give?
I’ll walk away to help you see
Our love is rolling down so easily
A one way street
You never give
I’ll walk away
So easily
A one way street