The sun is fading under blood-red sky
The reign of day is over
Night soon will break free.
They wake in the eerie glow of moonlight
Forgotten souls  beyond our sight.
World  that's gone forever
Long ago lost in their
Eyes that shine with mystery.
Last remaining shadows
Of lost time
Whisper in the moonlight.
Surprised you're waking in the morning.
Can't understand your feelings
And where d'you get these thoughts.
Inside your mind the voice is calling
For the night  to rise at your side
World that's gone forever
Long ago lost in their
Eyes that shine with mystery.
Last remaining shadows
Of lost time
Whisper in the moonlight.
So hear their voice
Sharing their yearning
Gift they're giving to you.
Hear their voice
Sharing their memories
Sacred secrets from past time.
World that's gone forever
Long ago lost in their
Eyes that shine with mystery.
Last remaining shadows
Of lost time
Whisper in the moonlight.
So hear their voice
Sharing their yearning
Gift they're giving to you.
Hear their voice
Sharing their memories
Sacred secrets from past
So hear their voice
Sharing their yearning
Gift they're giving to you.
Hear their voice
Sharing their memories -
Sacred secrets from past time.