I've been nothing but drinking and thinking yeah
Long since you been away
I don't think that I'm coming back
Boy I told you I'm done with that
You think you can do me so wrong
I'm not the one no
I'm not the one
Back In High School
Under the trees
We use to mess around
I'd feel you down
Right there in the streets damn
Those were the days baby
Now you barely look at me
Like you was never my lady
What has this come to be
Shit
I guess we grown apart
Went and seperated but you still up in my heart
And that will always be the case
You were my first one
No matter how the fuck we splite
I wish you nothin but love
But now I'm
Doing these shows and I'm making this money
I'm never stoppin for these hoes
All want me for money and shit
Got these new friends on deck when I cash in my checks
Late up on they rent feeling my heart poppin outta my chest
Aint no slippin in this game tho
They take advantage just to use you for the clout too
Thats why I keep my circle small
And I keep my friends close
Remembering to watch my enemies when they coming through
I don't think that I'm coming back
Boy I told you I'm done with that
You think you can do me so wrong
I'm not the one no
I'm not the one
I'm feeling blessed now
I'm Finally able to support my momma too
No more double shifts
No more stressing bout the rent shit
Complaining about the hunger and
Goin to bed starving
And its all thanks to you Momma
If it wasnt all for you beleiving in me
I'd probably be in jail doin 2-3
You Raised me up all on your own
Grew up without my poppa
And you put up with my shit
For that you know I'm grateful
Blessing with the family and friends all that I have
Got a loving cousin know I gotchu till the end.
Shout out to my crew
Adam and Dan Angelo Amin and Mack.
You know I got your backs
Shit we reppin Ottawa Ontario
We up at the Parliment jamming out all on the radio
I keep my circle small
And I rep my fam too
Remembering to watch our enemies when they coming through.
I don't think that I'm coming back
Boy I told you I'm done with that
You think you can do me so wrong
I'm not the one no
I'm not the one
I don't think that I'm coming back (Not coming around no more like that)
Boy I told you I'm done with that (Done with all that shit baby)
You think you can do me so wrong (Do Me so wrong like)
I'm not the one no (Not the one baby)
I'm not the one (Not the one baby)