Live in a time of straight sin we got black sheep that don’t fit in I’m like huhhh terrorists who wanna cut limbs don’t
zoom in to my true lens these loose ends are too grim to just comprehend I’m like huhhh oh lord it’s getting worse cops out
on that gang turf rich folks don’t share first got planned parents don’t need birth got prayers out and don’t see church
hands up and they shoot first another young life in that black Hurst I’m too hurt I’m like huhhh…
Ya’ll better come my way  ya’ll better come way okay and say ya’ll better come my way I’m gonna make a statement day by day
Peace signs peace signs up put em in the air and go rise up yeah
Peace signs  peace signs up put em in the air and go rise up yeah
Live in a time in true greed we got kids here who can’t write and read I’m like huhhh disgust for that mistrust say one
word and your handcuffed don’t call bluff and you’ll get struck and you’re in court like huhhh live life with no limits my
way no gimmicks pro league no scrimmage crunch time and I finish I’m that superstar no blemish I just own this no tenant
you that background no sentence I’m the statement good riddance.
Ya’ll better come my way ya’ll better come way okay and say ya’ll better come my way I’m gonna make a statement day by day
Peace signs peace signs up put em in the air and go rise up yeah
Stand up rise up peace signs up now whutsup
Live in a time of lost hope we got no ropes for that down slope we got many with plenty that say nope we got refugees on
broke boats I’m like huhhhh real life with no TV millionaires stay greedy no love and there’s no grub we got the homeless saying feed me…
Ya’ll better come my way ya’ll better come way okay and say ya’ll better come my way I’m gonna make a statement day by day
Peace signs peace signs up put em in the air and go rise up yeah